http://www.inlandtarp.com/privacy-statement

HOMEPAGE
Sign In. New Customer? Start Here.
Privacy Statement
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for inlandtarp.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent
this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization (and our network of dealers and
distributors), other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. We may forward your contact information to a dealer in your area who can coach you on the proper use of the product you
purchase (or are considering purchasing) in order to get maximum performance from that product. If you ask us not to forward any information we will respect your request.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of
your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or
customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Orders
We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date).
This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site
and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore
disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used
to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 800-346-7744 or via email.
“How we do business is more important than what business we do”.
Disclaimers
Errors and Ommissions: Inland Tarp & Liner (ITL®), LLC is not responsible for typographical, pricing or photographic errors.
Prices and specifications are subject to change without notice.
Finished Fabricated Goods: For ALL FABRICATED PRODUCTS there is a +/- 5% tolerence in total width and length of finished product.
Discounts, Coupons & Special Promotions: Cannot be combined with other coupons, discounts, promotions or special negotiated pricing.
Valid for online checkout only. Not applicable on prior orders. Subject to change without notice. Not redeemable for cash. Limited to stock on hand.
Looking for our Hay Tarp Rental & Covering company, ITC Services? Head over to their website: ITC Services, Inc.
Terms of Use    Privacy Statement
© 2004-2020 Inland Tarp & Liner (ITL®), LLC. All Rights Reserved.
